The greatest battle that never happened!
Flight World War II is a action, science fiction, war
film directed by Emile Edwin Smith.
International Flight 42 is on course, when all of a sudden a
massive and weird storm crops up around the plane.
This sends the plane back in time to the year 1940-
smack dab in the middle of WWII!
Now, the crew and passengers must not only find a way back to
their time, but fight off the Axis powers.
William Strong, played by Faran Tahir.
Nigel Sheffield, played by Robbie Kay.
Cameron Hicks, played by Aqueela Zoll.
Daniel Prentice, played by Matias Ponce.
Hector, played by Alberto Barros Jr..
Theresa, played by Vi Flaten.
The fall of Denmark in April 1940 left the Danish colony of Greenland an unoccupied territory of an occupied nation, under
the possibility of seizure by the United Kingdom, United States or Canada, a Dominion of the British Empire.
From 1941 until 1945, the United States established numerous and extensive facilities for air and sea traffic in Greenland, as well
as radio beacons, radio stations, weather stations, ports, depots, artillery posts, and search-and-rescue stations.
The United States Coast Guard also provided a considerable
portion of civilian resupply along both coasts.
Economically, Greenland traded successfully with the United States, Canada and Portugal, which, supplemented by
the cryolite exports, caused a reanimation and permanent realignment of the island's economy.
The tone is thought_provoking.